Okay.
Test, test, Test.
Okay, we're good.
This is the final thing I think I've explained in
this part in this file called dependency injection.
And so I explained it in these notes at the very first time.
We see depends mentioned.
So what's dependency injection in fast pi?
I've put some things here that will help you
out, but, i've also added A-T-L-D-R version.
If you just want a summary for it.
What I'll read with you now is actually the TLDR of
the TLDR is that when we put Depends like this, sorry.
As a parameter and a function, we basically, we can
basically think that this function is saying the
following, I depend on running this function, the function.
So it depends, I depend on running this
function first to proceed with my logic.
So let's take this as an example.
Register user when they, when the front end cause
a request for the back end for this endpoint.
We, sorry, we run this function, but before we run
this function, we see if there's any dependencies.
And there is dependency on validate_cors function.
So we first, first run validate_cors
function, which I'll show to you in a second.
And the return value of this function, we
we put it in this boolean called cors_ok.
Okay?
Okay.
So this is what depends mean.
And let's see, what validate_cors
to get a feel of what's happening.
Basically it just checks that the origins from which
the request comes from is within the Origins list.
Remember the Origins list?
The one in end of example over here in here?
This one?
Yeah.
So we check that from this function, which I showed
you previously, and the rest of Origins that we have.
We check the incoming origin from the request
parameter and see if the, like the header of
origin or host in it, whichever header in it.
If the values of this header is in the list of allowed origins.
Okay.
Then we're good to go.
Otherwise we raise an exception.
Okay.
Of incoming origin host and we say, what?
The request isn't coming, is not in the
origin list, the allowed origin list.
One might ask why do we do as function specifically for this
even though we have this code right here that I showed you,
privacy, the middleware where we add list of allowed origins.
You are right.
We have that.
But I think because I'm not the one who
initially add this, I think the main reason for
this is for any extra checks that we can do.
To bi maybe bypass this header thing.
So for example, what we're, the logic we're doing
here is that we're checking for another thing, like
not just the growth default origin or host headers.
No, we're just checking for a custom header that we put and
to see if it has certain values based on certain environment.
Then we'll also allow it to return through.
So if we are adding additional logic that we want
to check and based on it, allow the function to run.
We can call this function validate_cors.
Okay?
And we can use dependency injection like I showed you before.
So that's the reason we use this.
And we, you see this in everywhere basically.
Like you see almost all the functions that we have at feedback.
All of them, all of the endpoints we use is logic.
Okay?
So that's something.
And also, you might have noticed that this.
Has the request object passed to it?
So this is passed implicitly.
Okay.
So in a function which is it depends function from a, from
an end point function you have the normal register request.
Okay?
So this is the object that comes from the front end, which
contains data with the same structure as this key value pairs.
And.
Implicitly, we also get a request object here.
We don't need it, we just need this.
So we just code this value and that's it.
But in here we need it.
So in here we explicitly put it as a parameter so
that when it's sent to us from the front end and
when we run this we technically also receive that,
the normal request info from the front end as well.
Okay?
So that's something to keep in mind.
That's why this part works here.
I think, I'm not sure about this.
Technically, if I, if we put in this guest settings, if
we put if we put also requests here, like rec call and
requests, I think it'll work as well like we did here.
But I'm not sure about this to be honest.
So yeah, but this is at least is a logic for this part.
This is here and this is the logic of the, depends.
You can see more info about it here.
And and yeah, we use that logic everywhere.
So for example in here, if it's not okay,
we're not going to register the user.
So if the request comes from any other host that's
not related to us, then we will decline that
request and we'll raise an a call is not permitted.
Error.
Okay.
Yeah, I don't think I need to explain much else in the file.
The only thing remaining to explain is just the endpoints
themselves, just to explain what end point each endpoint does.
And this you really can understand it just by reading
the, any comments here or just the overall doc.
Doc stringing is sufficient.
For example, he get all threads, retrieve all threads from that.
Again, I know I didn't explain what threads,
what the thread means, but this part will
come when they when I explain, I'm sorry.
When the agent of, I'm sorry.
The AI mode.
But yeah, but overall the, these the code here is
pretty self explainable and yeah, I think I think
what I suggest is if you really confuse in something
try to search it here first and then search it in the
ui in the front end repo and see what it's called.
Maybe that will help you have a sense of of, okay,
where does this lie in the grand scheme of things.
Okay.
So that's that's all regarding the main.py file.
I don't think there is anything else I can add here.
So yeah, next up will be will yeah, will probably be the
probably be the WhatsApp files before the logic of Ansari itself.
Itself.
Yeah.
And then we'll we'll go to the AI model and
then simultaneous fives, and we'll be done.
Yay.